You'll Shake!--Quake! Laff, and Laff Some More
Heart to Heart is a comedy film directed by William Beaudine.
Princess Delatorre, young and beautiful widow of an Italian scion of royalty, returns with
her fortune to the small American town where she grew up as Ellen Gutherie.
Arriving by train a few days earlier than she
planned, Ellen is mistaken for Mrs.
Arden, a seamstress of doubtful repute from a neighboring town.
She carries on the deception for fun when her nearsighted
Aunt Katie and others believe she is Mrs.
Phil, her old sweetheart, recognizes her, however, and shows her his new invention,
a corkscrew that turns itself--a failure because of prohibition.
Ellen leaves, having heard how much store is set on her coming; she returns on the proper train,
elaborately made up as Princess Delatorre, and the big reception takes place as planned.
Then she and Phil return to Italy, where they
expect the corkscrew to be a success.
Princess Delatorre / Ellen Guthrie, played by Mary Astor.
Philip Lennox, played by Lloyd Hughes.
Aunt Katie Boyd, played by Louise Fazenda.
Uncle Joe Boyd, played by Lucien Littlefield.
Ruby Boyd, played by Thelma Todd.
Milt D'Arcy, played by Raymond McKee.
Heart to Heart is a 1928 American silent comedy film directed by William
Beaudine and produced and distributed by the First National company.
The film is preserved in the Library of Congress  collection, Packard Campus.
The tone is lighthearted.